buyvogue.com 2010-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Prada Sneakers, Prada Shoes, Gucci Sneakers, Gucci Shoes, Dolce Gabbana, Versace at BuyVogue - Online Fashion Store

[  
](http://www.buyvogue.com/prada-americas-cup-black-silver-men-sneakers-p-343.html)

I have just bought from here and I tell you, these are actua...

> PRIVACY RIGHTS OF WEBSITE VISITORS

>   
>  The following policy describes how we collect, protect and use information we receive from website visitors.   
>  BuyVogue.com is responsible for this privacy policy. Please note, that when you enter any sub-sites accessible through BuyVogue.com, they may have different privacy policies specific to those sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policy.   
> 

> Information Collected:    
> 
> 
>   * We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature. 
>   * When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, date of birth, e-mail address, mailing address, daytime phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously or purchase without registering. 
>   * Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies' ?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them. 
>   * We also receive and store click-stream data and other information about visits to our websites which may be combined with personal information you have provided. This information is used to analyze and improve the website experience. For more information see the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below. 
> 

> Use of Information    
>  We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:   
> 
> 
>   * To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. 
>   * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests. 
>   * To quickly process your transactions. 
>   * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. 
> 
  
>  If you have opted-in to receive BuyVogue e-mail, we may send you periodic e-mails from BuyVogue. If you would no longer like to receive, please cancel your account on our web site. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us. 

> Protection of Information    
> 
> 
>   * We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.
>   * Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 
>   * When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. 
>   * All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above. 
> 

> Cookies    
>  Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.   
> 
> 
>   * We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. 
>   * They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. 
>   * We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
>   * You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Mozilla Firefox or Internet Explorer) settings. 
>   * Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. 
>   * However, you can still place orders online as COD (Cash on Delivery) by contacting our customer service via Live Chat or Email.
> 

> Outside Parties    
> 
> 
>   * We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. 
>   * The term "outside parties" does not include BuyVogue.com. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting BuyVogue's business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. 
>   * We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. 
>   * However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 
> 

> Third Party Links    
> 
> 
>   * In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. 
>   * These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. 
>   * Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work). 
> 

> Change our Policy    
> 
> 
>   * This policy was last modified on January 1, 2008. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 
>   * Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. 
> 

> Your Feedback    
>  We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. 

> This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.   
>  By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.   
> 

> BuyVogue Inc.
